Finding Aid for the Cecil Sims
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous. Approximately 100 items, including flyers and blurbs, application forms, lists of names and addresses, and maps of France. Also included is a holographic paragraph signed by O.W. Holmes, dated March 8, 1931. (Box 25)
Smith, Hobert C., (1); Jan. 10, 1938; 10
Smith, Thos. O.H., (3); Oct. 9, 1934, Feb. 12, 1935, May 19, 1937; 10
Smith, W.J., (1); Jan. 26, 1957; 10
Smith, William P., (1); Aug. 28, 1933; 10
Smothers, James H. Jr., (1); (n.d.); 10
Snyder, Johnw., (3); Dec. 15, 1945, July 2, 1946, Mar. 9, 1948; 10
Sohn, Jang Nai, (1); Aug. 23, 1954; 10
Solomon, Marion B., (1); Sept. 15, 1961; 10
Spears, W.D., (1); May 23, 1961; 10
Sperry, Amelia, (1); July 14, 1948; 10
Sperry, M.L., (1); Dec. 9, 1937; 10
Sperry, Wesley H., (1); Aug. 19, 1965 (to Mrs. Joseph W. Byrns, Jr.); 10
Sprott, Evans, (1); May 5, 1960; 10
Stahlman, E.B. Jr., (1); Nov. 12, 1943; 10
Stahlman, James G., (8); Jan. 5, 1939 (to K.D. McKellar), Dec. 12, 1940, Apr. 19, 1943, Feb. 12, 1946, July 5, 1946, Sept. 11, 1950, Aug. 23, 1962, (n.d.); 10
Stahr, Elvis J. Jr., (1); Mar. 28, 1957; 10
Stainback, C.A., (1); (n.d.); 10
Stambaugh, John Howland, (2); June 22, 1959, Jan. 16, 1963; 10
Stanton, Hugh, (1); Sept. 28, 1955; 10
Stark, FrancisR., (1); Dec. 16, 1932; 10
Starr, Alfred, (1); Apr. 16, 1954; 10
Steecher, Joseph D., (1); (n.d.); 10
Steele, L.Y., (1); Dec. 7, 1949; 11
Steele, Thomas Jr., (1); Aug. 19, 1941; 11
Steele, Thomas Wardlaw, (1); Nov. 29, 1955; 11
Steele, Wardlaw, (2); Apr. 15, 1940, Apr. 15, 1940 (to Paul Savage); 11
Steger, William E., (1); June 18, 1963; 11
Stempler, Fay, (1); Aug. 14, 1948; 11
Stephenson, Gilbert T., (1); Nov. 14, 1936; 11
Stevens, L.B., (1); Jan. 28, 1946; 11
Stevenson, Alec B., (4); Feb. 18, 1933, Dec. 13, 1943, June 16, 1948, Feb. 23, 1949; 11
Stevenson, E.B. Jr., (3); Sept. 15, 1934, Dec. 12, 1934, Dec. 26, 1934; 11
Stevenson, Eldon Jr., (3); Dec. 6, 1962, May 24, 1963 (to Alexander Heard), Sept. 8, 1966; 11
Stewart, Roy B., (1); Sept,.o 22, 1964; 11
Stewart, Tom, (13); Apr. 1, 1939, Apr. 17, 1941, Mar. 14, 1942, June 8, 1942, Aug. 18, 1942, Oct. 8, 1943, Aug. 8, 1945, Sept. 24, 1945, Oct. 17, 1945, Oct. 31, 1945, Feb. 12, 1946, Mar. 13, 1946, Dec. 11, 1947; 11
Stillman, Dave, (1); (n.d.); 11
Stimson, D.C., (1); Dec. 26, 1934; 11
Stockel!, Mercer L., (1); Nov. 2, 1964; 11
Stonier, Harold, (1); May 1, 1937; 11
Strang, Carl, (6); Feb. 5, 1936, Jan. 18, 1936, Feb. 15, 1937, Oct. 4, 1954, June 29, 1958, Feb. 1, 1959; 11
Strother, W.Bruce, (3); Hay 18, 1965, Sept. 28, 1966, Mar. 7, 1967; 11
Stubbs, R.R., (1); Jan. 19, 1962; 11
Stumpf, Samuel Enoch, (2); Mar. 9, 1960, Dec. 6, 1960; 11
Sturdivant, Robert W., (1); Feb. 20, 1937; 11
Sullivan, Margaret R., (1); Sept. 25, 1962; 11
Sullivan, Robert, (1); July 24, 1939; 11
Summer, H.S., (1); Jan. 25, 1933; 11
Sutherland, E.A., (1); Feb. 12, 1951; 11
Sutherland, Mrs. M.B. DeGraw, (1); 11 (Dec. 17, 1962)
Swallows, W.L., (1); Mar. 21, 1944; 11
Swanson, C.E., (2); June 15, 1961, Aug. 10, 1961; 11
Swiggart, James M., (1); Mar. 29, 1965; 11
Swiggart, William H., (2); June 13, 1938, Apr. 7, 1965; 11
Swint, H.L., (1); Nov. 18, 1964; 11
Talley, Lucille Estelle, (2); Oct. 11, 1949, Feb. 10, 1951; 11
Tanner, T.W., (1); Aug. 12, 1933; 11
Tate, S. Shepherd, (1); Aug. 17, 1964; 11
Tatum, Sam Davia, (1); Sept. 12, 1947; 11
Taylor, c.lohn F., (1); July 4, 1956; 11
Taylor, R.L., (2); Dec. 7, 1934, Dec. 19, 1934; 11
Taylor, Robert C., (1); Apr. 23, 1962; 11
Taylor, Robert L., (4); May 9, 1934, June 8, 1934, Oct. 29, 1949, July 24, 1963; 11
Te1lotson, A.L. Jr., ~2); May 12, 1938, Sept. 25, 1941; 11
Thomas, Law Book Company, (1); Apr. 5, 1937; 11
Thomas, Albert H., (1); Dec. 2, 1933 (to Herbert Pearson); 11
Thomas, L.M., (2); May 2, 1939, Apr. 22, 1940; 11
Thomas, Murphy, (1); Sept.11, 1963; 11
Thomas, W.P., (1); July 16, 1934; 11
Thompson, Fred Dalton, (1); Feb. 23, 1966; 11
Thompson, Hannah C., (1); Sept. 14, 1956; 11
Thompson, Joe Jr., (1); Mar. 29, 1965; 11
Thompson, Mary R.’ (1); July 8, 1961; 11
Thompson, Neal L.’ (2); Oct. 26, 1934, Oct.
Thompson, R. Elmo, (2); Apr. 25, 1939, Mar.
Thorpe, William B., (1); May 23, 1948; 11
Tidman, J .H.’ (1); May 27, 1948; 11
Tidrow, Mary, (1); Nov. 21, 1961; 11
Tinnon, Frank R., (1); June 7, 1955; 11
Tipps, Maynard, (1); July 3, 1958; 11
Tipton, Jere T., (1); June 22, 1948; 11
Tipton, Nat, (3); Aug. 8, 1934, Feb. 13,1946, (n.d.); 11
Tirmenstin, M.G., (1); Jan. 29, 1936; 11
Tisdale, Wright, (1); Sept. 25, 1964; 11
Tobin, Jos. s., (1); Mar. 18, 1935 (to ueo. s. VanSchaick); 11
Tomlin, Hewitt P. Jr., (1); Jan. 26, 1961; 11
Tomlinson, Pride, (4); Dec. 18, 1940, July 16, 1948, Mar. 29, 1955, Oct. 10, 1962; 11
Touchstone, 0.0., (1); Apr. 21, 1944; 11
Trabue, Charles C., Jr., (1); Oct. 2, 1958; 11
Trautman, Herman L., (1); Apr. 21, 1962; 11
Trimble, Thomas, (1); May 31, 1954; 11
Truman, Harry s., (1); May 17, 1937; 11
Tupper, Vernon, (1); Sept. 5, 1936; 11
Turner, Chas. D., (2); Dec. 13, 1940, Oct. 17, 1941; 11
Turner, F.J., (1); Dec. 14, 1956; 11
Turner, G.F., (1); July 22, 1963; 11
Turner, Hill, (8); Aug. 15, 1934, Aug. 31, 1934, Feb. 15, 1935, Jan. 7, 1938 (to John Dawes Frierson), Mar. 14, 1938, June 4, 1941, Feb. 19, 1946, MaY 20, 1958; 11
Tye, Earl, (1); Aug. 4, 1961; 11
Uhler, Harold C., (2); May 6, 1933, May 6, 1933 (to John Ohman); 11
Upton, Wayne, (2); Sept. 13, 1951, May 10, 1954; 11?
The Vanderbilt Law Faculty, (1); (n.d.), (to Elsie and Eddie); 11
VanDyke, James W., (3); Feb. 9, 1934, Mar. 6, 1934, May 2, 1934; 11
VanNess, Francis T., (1); Sept. 29; 11
Vaughn, W.S., (3); May 16, 1960, May 31, 1960, May 29, 1961; 11
Volkert, George, (1); Apr. 1, 1966; 11
Voorhees, John H., (1); June 20, 1938; 11
Wade, John W., (4); Jan. 12, 1962 (to E.E. Bryant), Feb. 21, 1963 (to J. Clifton Owen), Mar. 26, 1963, Dec. 3, 1964; 11
Waggoner, Clarence L., (1); May 25, 1948; 11
Wakefield, Henrys., (1); Dec. 23, 1932; 11
walker, Matthew, (2); Dec. 2?, 1949, Apr. 4, 1950 (toM. Don Clawson); ll
Wallace, Richard, (2); Mar. 14, 1947, Apr. 5, 1952; ll
Waller, Thomas S., (2); Jan. 30, 1934, Feb. 11, 1957; 11
Walsh, James F. Jr., (4); May 1, 1961 (to Estes Kefauver), May 1, 1961 (to Albert Gore), May 8, 1961, (n.d.); 11
Walters, H.S., (1); June 24, 1948; 11
Ware, W. Porter, (2); Aug. 23, 1941, Mar. 19, 1955; 11
Warfield, Francis H., (1); Dec. 13, 1954; 11
Warfield, WilliamS. III, (7); Aug. 8, 1936, Aug. 26, 1936, Sept. 21, 1936, Oct. 8, 1936, Nov. 10, 1936, Nov. 21, 1936, Nov. 24, 1936; 11
Warmack, Lillie, (1); June 24, 1940; 11
Warren, Ed. B., (1); Jan. 29, 1958; 11
Warren, Fuller, (1); Jan. 2, 1949; 11
Warren, I.M., (1); Aug. 25, 1933; 11
Warren, W.K., (1); Oct. 11, 1961; 11
Washington Square Galleries, Inc., (l); (n.d.); 11
Wasson, S.E., (2); Dec. 4, 1940, Feb. 19, 1946; 11
Watkins, Mary E., (1); Aug. 8, 1967; 11
Watson, Emery, W., (2); Sept. 24, 1937; May 21, 1940; 11
Watson, Jim, (1); June 24, 1959; 11
Watson, Lucille, (1); Apr. 4, 1938; 11
Watson, Neill M., (1); May 10, 1934; 11
Wear, D.N., (2); June 11, 1964, Oct. 5, 1964; 11
Weaver, Herbert, (1); June 17, 1955; 11
Webb, Bernice, (1); Mar. 31, 1936; 11
Webb, T.D., (4); Jan. 21, 1933, June 24, 1933, June 22, 1933, June 24, 1935 (to Joseph W. Byrns); 11
Webb, W.R., (10); Aug. 23, 1937, Aug. 26, 1937, Apr. 15, 1938, Oct. 12, 1938, Dec. 8, 1938, Apr. 11, 1939, Apr. 22, 1939, Sept. 5, 1940, Nov. 26, 1941, Dec. 21, 1946; 11
Weissman, Samuel, (6); Sept. 8, 1950, Sept. 22, 1950, Sept. 14, 1951, Sept. 2, 1952, Sept. 19, 1952, Aug. 31, 1953; 11
Welwood, John C., (1); Apr. 15, 1938; 11
West, Olin Jr., (1); Jan. 19, 1955; 11
West, C.H., (1); Jan. 13, 1960
West, Sam C., (1); Apr. 20, 1963; 11
Wetherby, Lawrence w., (2); Dec. 19, 1952, Jan. 20, 1953 (to Frank Glement); 11
Whaley, Lula, (1); June 30, 1938; 11
Wheat, Maude Harvey, (2); Oct. 3, 1933, May 3, 1934; 11
Whitaker, M.N., (2); Apr. 13, 1938, Apr. 13, 1938 (to Elnora Grizzard); 11
Whitaker, Phil B., (4); Nov. 26, 1934, Apr. 5, 1938, Apr. 27, 1938, June 8, 1948 (to Howard McGrath); 11
Whitaker, Sam E., (1); Apr. 6, 1946; 11
Whitaker, W.L. Jr., (1); Apr. 20, 1965; 11
White, Joseph R Jr., (1); Nov. 7, 1958; 11
White, Olin, (1); Feb. 4, 1965; 11
White, Hobert H., (1); (n.d.); 11
White, Weldon B., (1); (n.d.); 11
Whitley, H.A., (1); 11
Whitlow, Henry 0., (1); Jan. 28, 1957; 11
Wicker, William, (1); Apr. 16, 1952; 11
Wigginton, Martha Teague, (1); Mar. 25, 1945; 11
Wigginton, Matts., (1); Mar. 21, 1967; 11
Wilbur, Albert A., (1); Apr. 17, 1944; 11
Wiles, Mrs. Marvin, (1); Apr. 13, 1948; 11
Wilkerson, J.C., (4); May 15, 1934, May 23, 1934, May 30, 1934, June 19, 1934; ll
Wilkerson, Joe, (1); Jan. 23, 1941 (to Garland Turner); 11
Willey, Harold B., (l); Feb. 20, 1936; 11
Williams, Charlie, (1); Apr. 6, 1966; ll
Williams, Frank, (1); Apr. 29, 1964; 11
Williams, Harding E., (4); Nov. 25, 1936, Dec. 9, 1954, Mar. 19, 1956, Nov. 15, 1957; 11
Williams, Henry Newton, (1); Nov. 15, 1963; 11
Williams, J.D., (1); Jan. 22, 1951 (to John E. Ivey, Jr.); 11
Williams, Nell Shriver, (1); (n.d.); 11
Willis, Anne W., (1); Mar. 25, 1954; 11
Wills, Jesse E., (l); May 30, 1963; 11
Wilson, A., (3); Sept. 11, 1941, Aug. 22, 1947, Oct. 7, 1947; 11
Wilson, Buford G., (1); Jan. 21, 1943; 11
Wilson, E. Bright, (2); Apr.21, (n.d.); 11
Wilson, .Felix Z. II, (l); Apr. 4, 1963; 11
Wilson, I.H., (1); July 9, 1934; 11
Wingfield, Sam, (2); Dec. 16, 1954; Dec. 29, 1954; 11
Winick, Ben R., (1); Apr. 23, 1943; 11
Winters, Halph L., (1); Dec. 17, 1956; ll
Witham, Henry, B., (3); Apr. 14, 1939 (to Ben F. Alexander), May 5, 1939 (to tlen F. Alexander), May 9, 1939; ll
Witsell, Edward F., (1); Jan. 28, 1946 (to Mrs. C.E. Saxon); ll
Witt, Raymond B. Jr., (1); June 10, 1964; 11
Wood, Mary Sherer, (4); Mar. 27, 1961, Nov. 1, 1961, Apr. 6, 1962, May 10, 1962; 11
Wood, Sandy, (1); June 3, 1940; 11
Woods, Emma Beard, (1); Mar. 26, 1967; 11
Woodward, Russel, (1); May 9, 1934; 11
Worthington, E.H., (l); Feb. 9 (n.d.) (to Mrs. C. Sims); 11
Wright, A.E., (l); Sept. 6, 1963; 11
Wroton, Lang, (3); Sept. 9, 1962, Sept. 17, 1962, Oct. 17, 1962; ll
WynKoop, G.P. Jr., (l); Dec. 12, 1933; 11
Young, Wilbur S., (2); June 18, 1937, July 12, 1937; ll
Youngblood, Sam, (l); Apr. 21, 1961; 11
Youree, Sam L., (l); (n.d.); ll
Zerfoss, Kate, (l); Feb. 2, 1934; ll
Ziegler, Frank W., (l); Sept. 13, 1961; ll
Letters with I ncomplete Signatures (ie. signed with initials only or with 1 name only) Agnes, (l); Mar. 8, 1967; 11
Ben, (1); Mar. 27, 1940; 11
Booton, (1); Jan. 30; 11
Brad, (1); (n.d.); 11
Bud, (1); Mar. 4, 1945; 11
C., (3); July 4, 1936, July 6, 1936, July 8, 1936; 11
Cornelia, (2); Nov. 15, 1940, June 27, 1965; 11
Dave, (1); July 29, 1941; 11
David, (2); Dec. 16, 1962, Nov. 27, 1963; 11
Dick, (1); (n.d.); 11
Elmo, (1); Nov. 30, 1943; 11
Elsie & Ed, (1); Jan. 22, 1964; 11
Felix, (1); Dec. 1; 11
Francis, (1); (n.d.); 11
Frazer, (1); Feb. 25, 1966; 11
Harry and David, (l); Nov. 25, 1958; 11
Jenny, (l); (n.d.); 11
Jim, (1); (n.d.); 11
Judson & Frances, (l); (n.d.); 11
Julia, (1); Oct. 24; 11
Mark, (1); (n.d.); 11
Nick, (1); (n.d.); 11
Red, (1); May 23, 1962; 11
Robby, (2); Dec. 14, 1934, Jan. 4, 1935; 11
Shearer, (1); (n.d.); 11
Tom, (1); July 2, 1948 (to J. Percy Priest); 11
V.H., (1); Feb. 13, 1946; 11
W.C., (1); Feb. 3, 1964; 11
W.W.B., (1); (n.d.); 11
Wilson, (1); Apr. 16, 1919; 11
9 Letters Without Signatures (Chronologically Arranged- Feb. 12, 1936- Feb. 28, 1948).
17 Letters With Illegible Signatures (Chronologically Arranged - Oct. 4, 1933 - (v1arch 12, 1963).